

## **Arabela Estela Rojas Castro**

\_\_\_\_\_

### Career Summary

Arabela is a Front End Developer with 8 years of experience, she has worked in Marketing, IT, Banking, Education, Telecom industries in Peru and USA, She has creativity for resolve, create and adaptation to different environments and culture. She has the ability of leadership, being responsible for managing teamwork, good communicator and always looking for innovation and help to grow the project. Also experienced in Design.

## **Summary of Qualifications**

#### Proficient In:

- HTML5 (adv)
- CSS3 (adv)
- jQuery (adv)
- Git Flow (adv)
- BEM (adv)
- SASS (adv)

- Tailwind CSS (int)
- Atomic Design (adv)
- Responsive Design (adv)
- JavaScript (int)
- React JSX (int)
- Typescript (int)
- Google APis (int)

- CSS Modules (int)
- Kanban (int)
- Agile methods (int)
- Photoshop (adv)
- Illustrator (int)
- Figma (int)

### Languages

- Spanish (native)
- English (intermediate B1)

### Career History

# Globant, Lima, Perú

Web UI Developer

ΙT

Responsibilities:

- Adding methodologies that help you to create reusable components and code sharing, implementing helper structure to organize and be more productive with the components itself.
- ullet As a TL I was in charge of assignment manager, organizing data of the team and ceremonies, helping and taking care of the quality of the project.
- Develop features on demand to get on time with the goal of a sprint.
- Support the main team and design team to organize the task of each sprint

Used Applications/Technologies: Jira, Trello, Google Apps, React JSX. Git, Github

Feb. 2021- Current



# Burns The Agency, Lima, Perú

Jan. 2019 – Feb. 2021

Front End Developer

Telecommunications, Marketing

### Responsibilities:

- Manage a team of developers and support them in some features and working content updates on Wordpress / Oracle CMS / Vtex.
- Organizing data of the team and ceremonies before every sprint.
- Development of new Landings for campaign and promos with JavaScript and Jquery, working from scratch with the client team on Vtex to generate a new ecommerce in Perú: <a href="https://catalogo.entel.pe">https://catalogo.entel.pe</a>
- Development of new Landings for short-term projects and support the team of developers in <a href="http://www.entel.pe/">http://www.entel.pe/</a>

**Used Applications/Technologies:** Jira, Trello, Google Apps, Vanilla JS, Wordpress, Vtex, Oracle CMS, Git, Github

LIQUID, Lima, Perú

Sep. 2017 – Dic. 2018

Front End Developer

Telecommunications, Marketing

## Responsibilities:

- Worked on re-skin for a Peruvian Bank: www.trabajaeninterbank.pe
- Worked in construction on a new web page of celima. https://www.celima-trebol.com/puntos-venta
- Working on a Map of sites around Peru to find a good place to park, google maps was implemented in this project. <a href="http://www.losportalesestacionamientos.com.pe/ubicanos">http://www.losportalesestacionamientos.com.pe/ubicanos</a>
- Frequently attend meetings and training with my IT area, and explain some themes related to development
- Development of new Landings for short-term projects and support the team of developers in <a href="http://www.entel.pe/">http://www.entel.pe/</a>

**Used Applications/Technologies:** Trello, Google Apps, Vanilla JS, JQuery, Wordpress, Vtex, Oracle CMS, Git, Github

#### **Education**

**Laboratoria**, Lima, Perú Front End Developer Jan. 2015 – Jun. 2015